https://imedx.com/au/terms/

Skip to content
Close Menu
Terms of Use
This website has been developed as a service of iMedX Australia, Inc. (“iMedX Australia”). By accessing and using the web site located at https://imedx.com/au/ (the “Web Site”), you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use (hereinafter, the “Terms” or “Agreement”) in effect at the time of each such access or other use. You also acknowledge that iMedX Australia may, from time to time, in its sole discretion and without notification to you, change these Terms. You should review the Terms each time you visit or use the Web Site. If you do not agree to these Terms, do not use the Web Site. As used in these Terms of Use, “we” includes iMedX Australia and any third-party vendors we hire to assist in the administration of the Web Site, the collection, cataloging and/or analysis of data, and/or the processing or handling of any visitor transactions.
No Medical Advice and Disclaimer as to Accuracy of Information.
All information on the Web Site is for informational purposes only, and is not medical advice or a substitute for medical care or consultation.
License and Access to the Web Site
No person under the age of eighteen (18) is authorised to access or use this Web Site. User access to, and use of, the Web Site is subject to all applicable federal, state and local laws and regulations. Use of this Web Site is void where prohibited. By using this Web Site, you represent and warrant that you are eighteen (18) years of age and that you have the right, authority and capacity to enter into this Agreement and abide by the Terms.
iMedX Australia grants you a limited, non-transferable license to access and use for non-commercial purposes the Web Site. Such limited license shall enable you to use the Web Site for informational purposes. This license shall not include any resale or commercial use of the Web Site or its contents; any derivative use of the Web Site or its contents; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. You may not frame or utilise framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of iMedX Australia or our affiliates without our prior express written consent.
We make no guarantees regarding the availability of the Web Site. Furthermore, we reserve the right, within our sole discretion, to discontinue the Web Site. You agree that we will not be liable to you for any such discontinuance or modification of the Web Site. Any rights not expressly granted by these Terms are reserved by us.
You are under no obligation to use or continue to use the Web Site and may temporarily or permanently cease using the Web Site without notice to iMedX Australia. Any use of the Web Site, or any portion thereof, in violation of the foregoing shall constitute a violation of these Terms and may result in, among other things, termination or suspension of your rights to use the Web Site or any portion thereof.
Click-Through Agreements
Before using certain areas of the Web Site you may be asked to indicate your acceptance of additional special terms and conditions by clicking a button marked “I Accept,” “I Agree,” “Okay,” “I Consent” or other words or actions that similarly acknowledge your consent or acceptance of a Click-Through Agreement. To the extent there is a conflict between these Terms and any Click-Through Agreement, the Click-Through Agreement will govern.
Account Registration and Payments
In order to access certain portions of the Web Site, you may be required to register and create a membership account (“Account”) with iMedX Australia. Information gathered through the registration process and any other information related to your Account will be subject to these Terms as well as to our Privacy Policy. You represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years old and that all information provided by you when creating your Account is true, accurate and complete and that you will maintain, at all times, true, accurate and complete information related to your Account. Information related to your Account should be maintained by you in a confidential manner, as you are solely responsible for the usage of your Account by any third parties with respect to the Web Site. It is your responsibility to advise us if you are aware of any unauthorised access to your Account or if your Account information has been made available by you to third-parties in a manner that may result in unauthorised usage of the Account. In our sole and absolute discretion, we may terminate your Account for any reason (including for reasons related to unlawful or unauthorised usage) and we are under no obligation to retain a record of your Account or any data or information that you may have stored by means of the Account.
Restrictions on Your Use
All content within the Web Site and any materials made available on these pages for downloading, if any, are the property of iMedX Australia and/or its affiliates or other third parties. The Web Site and portions of the Web Site are protected by copyright and trademark laws. This Agreement does not grant any license to modify or alter the materials on the Web Site that are viewed, downloaded or otherwise accessed by you. You shall keep intact all proprietary notices, including copyright notices, contained on any downloadable materials. You shall be solely liable for any damages resulting from any infringement of copyright, trademark, or other proprietary right, or any and all harm resulting from your use of the Web Site.
To the extent applicable, when accessing the Web Site, you are required to use the security procedures currently or hereafter maintained by us to confirm that only authorised users have access to certain information provided at, or contained in, the Web Site. You are prohibited from utilising alter-egos or other disguised identities when accessing the Web Site. All forms of indirect and ‘spoofed’ access are strictly prohibited.
Do not submit, post or otherwise transmit via the Web Site information that is proprietary or confidential of third parties (whether by law or by contract) or that you otherwise do not have the legal right to use. Any information, content or other material, including, but not limited to, any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, plans, ideas, user reviews or the like, which you send to us will be treated as being non-confidential and non-proprietary. We assume no obligation to protect confidential or proprietary information (other than those outlined in our Privacy Policy) from disclosure.
Intellectual Property Ownership
Any and all intellectual property rights associated with the Web Site, including, without limitation, any inventive concepts, know-how, publicity rights, trademarks, trade-dress, trade secrets, copyrights and patents (“Intellectual Property”) are the sole property of iMedX Australia or third parties. Except as otherwise expressly authorised by these Terms, you may not copy, reproduce, modify, lease, loan, sell, create derivative works from, upload, transmit, or distribute the Intellectual Property of the Web Site in any way without the express written consent of iMedX Australia or the express written consent of the appropriate third party, as applicable. Except as provided herein, iMedX Australia does not grant to you any express or implied rights to iMedX Australia or any third party’s Intellectual Property.
Privacy Policy
Any personal information or other information about you collected by iMedX Australia through, or in connection with, this Web Site is subject to our Privacy Policy. The iMedX Australia Privacy Policy is incorporated into the terms of this Agreement by this reference. As indicated in these Terms, this Web Site is designed for adults of legal age (18 years and over). For questions about our online privacy policy for children please refer to the Privacy Policy.
Links
This Web Site may provide or include links to other world wide web sites or resources. While iMedX Australia attempts to provide links only to third-party websites that comply with all applicable laws and regulations and iMedX Australia’s standards, please understand that the content on these third-party websites is subject to change without notice to iMedX Australia. Because we have no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that iMedX Australia is not responsible for the availability of such external sites, or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT iMedX Australia SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS CAUSED OR ALLEGED TO BE CAUSED BY OR IN CONNECTION WITH USE OF OR RELIANCE ON ANY SUCH CONTENT OR SITES AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH ANY SUCH SITE OR RESOURCE.
iMedX Australia prohibits caching of any portion of the Web Site and any unauthorised hypertext links to the Web Site. We reserve the right to disable any unauthorised links or frames. If you desire to provide a hyperlink from your website to the Web Site, you must contact iMedX Australia to discuss mutually agreeable terms for such hyperlink.
Exclusion of Warranty
iMedX Australia MAKES NO WARRANTY OF ANY KIND REGARDING THE WEB SITE AND/OR ANY MATERIALS PROVIDED ON THE WEB SITE, ALL OF WHICH ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. iMedX Australia DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, CURRENCY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY OF THE CONTENT OR DATA FOUND ON THE WEB SITE AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND THOSE ARISING BY STATUTE OR OTHERWISE IN LAW OR FROM A COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE. iMedX Australia DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE WEB SITE, ITS SERVERS OR ANY E-MAIL SENT FROM IT ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
NEITHER iMedX Australia, NOR ITS AFFILIATES, MAKES ANY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR GUARANTEES REGARDING (1) THE OPERATION OR PERFORMANCE OF THE WEB SITE OR SERVICES, OR (2) THE INTERNET GENERALLY.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION AND THAT MAY NOT BE LIMITED BY THESE TERM, PROVIDED HOWEVER YOU AGREE AND ACKNOWLEDGE THAT TO THE EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, YOU WAIVE ANY SUCH STATUTORY RIGHTS WITH RESPECT TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES.
Limitation of Liability
iMedX Australia ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY, AND SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR, ANY DAMAGES TO, OR VIRUSES THAT MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR OTHER PROPERTY ON ACCOUNT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR BROWSING IN THE WEB SITE OR YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIALS, DATA, TEXT, IMAGES, VIDEO OR AUDIO FROM THE WEB SITE. IN NO EVENT SHALL iMedX Australia BE LIABLE FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS, CLAIM, DAMAGES, OR ANY SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS), WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE, WHICH ARISES OUT OF OR IS IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH ANY USE OF THE WEB SITE OR CONTENT FOUND THEREIN.
Jurisdictional Issues
Although this Web Site is accessible worldwide, not all information, products or services discussed or referenced herein are available to all persons or in all geographic locations. This Web Site is controlled and operated by iMedX Australia from its offices within Atlanta, Georgia. iMedX Australia makes no representation that materials on the Web Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this Web Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.
Choice of Law and Forum
These Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Georgia, United States of America, excluding its conflicts of law rules. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to these Terms shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the County of Fulton, State of Georgia, and you further agree and submit to the exercise of personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating such claim or action.
Indemnity and Release
By using this Web Site, you agree to indemnify iMedX Australia and its partners, officers, employees and agents and hold them harmless from any and all claims and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising from your use of the Web Site. By using the Web Site, you are hereby agreeing to release iMedX Australia and its partners, officers, employees and agents from any and all claims, demands, debts, obligations, damages (actual or consequential), costs and expenses of any kind or nature whatsoever, whether known or unknown, suspected or unsuspected, disclosed or undisclosed, that you may have against them arising out of or in any way related to your use of the Web Site.
Severability and Integration
Unless otherwise specified herein, this Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and iMedX Australia with respect to this Web Site and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals (whether oral, written, or electronic) between you and iMedX Australia with respect to this Web Site. If any part of these Terms is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties and the remaining portion shall remain in full force and effect.
Changes to the Terms
We may periodically modify and supplement these Terms and the notice provided to you will be the updating of these Terms. You are responsible for regularly checking these Terms for revisions. All amended Terms become effective upon our posting to the Web Site, and any use of the Web Site after such revisions have been posted signifies your consent and agreement to the modified Terms.
This Agreement was last modified and is effective as of August 6, 2018.
We are always here to help. Send us a message
